export const Data = {
    round: 1,
    question: "Name something you eat after a strong tequila",
    answers: [{
      id: 1, 
      ans: "Lime"
    }, {
      id: 2,
      ans: "A meal"
    }, {
      id: 3,
      ans: "Genitals"
    }, {
      id: 4,
      ans: "More tequila"
    }, {
      id: 5,
      ans: "Vomit"
    }]
  }

//   "1": {
//     "question": "Name something people do to sober up in a hurry",
//     "answers": ["Coffee", "Shower", "Vomit", "Coke / Meth / Drugs", "Eat"]
//   },
//   "2": {
//    "question": "Name an occupation in which you meet a lot of drunk people",
//    "answers": ["bartender", "Cop", "Stripper", "Sales", "Uber / Taxi driver"]
//   },
//   "3": {
//     "question": "Name an AA members least favorite step",
//     "answers": ["Fourth", "Ninth", "Eighth", "First", "Thirteenth"]
//   },
//   "4": {
//     "question": "Name a place to hide your stash",
//     "answers": ["Where am i?", "What did i do?", "Oh shit / fuck!", "Who is that?", "Not again"]
//   },
//   "5": {
//     "question": "Most common item lost after a night of binge drinking",
//     "answers": ["Money / Wallet", "Phone", "Keys", "Morals / dignity", "Freedom"]
//   },
//   "6": {
//     "question": "Where is the best place to get drunk",
//     "answers": ["Home", "Bar", "Anywhere", "Party", "Prison"]
//   },
//   "7": {
//     "question": "After a campout, what luxury item are you most looking forward to",
//     "answers": ["Shower / bath", "Bed", "electronics", "Toilet", "Sex with your Actual S.O."]
//   },
//   "8": {
//     "question": "Name someone you wouldnt want to see nude",
//     "answers": ["Drumph (D. Trump)", "Dad", "Mom", "Grandparent", "Tipper Gore"]
//   },
//   "9": {
//     "question": "Name something you smoke",
//     "answers": ["Weed", "Cigarettes", "Crack", "Salmon", "Dick"]
//   },
//   "10": {
//     "question": "In L.A. County jail, word is you can trade 200 cigs for...",
//     "answers": ["Sex", "Alcohol / Drugs", "Food", "Stamps", "Protection"]
//   },
//   "11": {
//     "question": "Name a reason it hurts when you pee",
//     "answers": ["STD", "UTI", "Sex", "Yeast infection", "Cancer"]
//   },
//   "12": {
//     "question": "Best food to eat drunk",
//     "answers": ["Pizza", "Tacos", "Fries / Tots", "Nachos", "Hamburger"]
//   },
//   "13": {
//     "question": "Name a city you think is most visited in the U.S.",
//     "answers": ["NYC", "LA", "San Francisco", "Portland", "Las Vegas"]
//   },
//   "14": {
//     "question": "Name something sticky",
//     "answers": ["Semen", "Gum", "Honey", "Glue", "Situations"]
//   },
//   "15": {
//     "question": "Name something a newcomer needs most",
//     "answers": ["Support / Love / Something sticky", "Big Book", "Sponsor", "Willingness", "Desperation"]
//   },
//   "16": {
//     "question": "Inappropriate place to occupy drunk",
//     "answers": ["Church", "School", "Work", "Parents", "Senate hearing"]
//   },
//   "17": {
//     "question": "Name a place that might have a waiting list",
//     "answers": ["Restaurant", "Rehab", "College class", "Doctors office", "Heaven"]
//   },
//   "18": {
//     "question": "Womans Name starting with the letter J",
//     "answers": ["Jennifer / Jenny", "Jessica", "Julie", "Janet", "Jewel"]
//   },
//   "19": {
//     "question": "Name a U.S. State that has big mountains",
//     "answers": ["Colorado", "Oregon", "Montana", "California", "You mom"]
//   },
//   "20": {
//     "question": "A preformer or group whos epic-ness spans generations",
//     "answers": ["Beatles", "Rolling Stones", "Led Zepplin", "Aerosmith", "Why is Jimi not on this list?!"]
//   },
//   "21": {
//     "question": "Name something that comes in nuggets (other than your mom)",
//     "answers": ["Chicken", "Gold", "Weed", "Poop", "Knowledge"]
//   },
//   "22": {
//     "question": "Brands of expensive Alcohol",
//     "answers": ["Patron", "Hennessy", "Grey Goose", "Johnney Walker", "Glennlevet"]
//   },
//   "23": {
//     "question": "Something you dont want to hear after a one night stand",
//     "answers": ["I have an STD", "I'm preggers", "Whats your name", "I love you", "Honey, im home"]
//   },
//   "24": {
//     "question": "Name a type of fish people order at a fine resturaunt",
//     "answers": ["Salmon", "Tuna", "Swordfish", "Mahi Mahi", "Halibut"]
//   },
//   "25": {
//     "question": "According to Women: What is the most important element in a relationship",
//     "answers": ["Trust", "Communication", "Honesty", "Penis size", "Respect"]
//   },
//   "26": {
//     "question": "Method for not drinking when you really want to",
//     "answers": ["Call someone", "Go to a meeting", "Sex", "Heroin", "Steps"]
//   },
//   "27": {
//     "question": "Name a reason you get a new sponsor",
//     "answers": ["They relapse", "One of you moves", "Lack of trust", "Sponsor hits on me", "They bang your S.O."]
//   },
//   "28": {
//     "question": "Best domestic beer",
//     "answers": ["Budweiser", "Coors", "PBR", "Rolling Rock", "None"]
//   },
//   "29": {
//     "question": "Name a place you meet with your sponsor to do your steps",
//     "answers": ["Their house", "Coffee shop", "Restaurant", "Park", "A meeting"]
//   },
//   "30": {
//     "question": "Name the best AA conf that has ever been attended",
//     "answers": ["ACYPAA", "WACYPAA", "OSYPAA", "ORCYPAA", "ICYPAA"]
//   },
//   "31": {
//     "question": "In one word, describe AA coffee",
//     "answers": ["Strong", "Cheap", "Gross / shitty / terrible", "Free", "Gateway-drug"]
//   },
//   "32": {
//     "question": "Name an injury commonly sustained whilst intoxicated",
//     "answers": ["broken bone", "Sprain", "bruise", "Black eye", "Head trauma"]
//   },
//   "33": {
//     "question": "Most common excuse to not answer your phone",
//     "answers": ["In the bathroom / toliet / shower", "Driving", "Sleeping", "Didnt hear it", "Busy"]
//   },
//   "34": {
//     "question": "Name something you shouldnt opperate under the influence",
//     "answers": ["Car", "heavy equipment", "Cell phone", "Power tools", "Bicycle"]
//   }
// }